lawdepot.ca 2018-09-06

# Privacy Policy | LawDepot

## LawDepot® Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment to your Privacy

LawDepot® is committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring that your visit to our website is completely secure.

If you have any questions or problems with any aspect of our privacy policy or its implementation, please contact our [ privacy officer](mailto:privacyofficer@lawdepot.com?Subject=Privacy%20Officer).

### Security of your Personal Information

To maintain the security of your information, we use the Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocol with 128-bit or higher encryption strength to transmit sensitive information. This is the same technology used in transmitting sensitive information by banks, governments, and online businesses such as Amazon.com and eBay.

Once the information is in our system, it is accessible to authorized LawDepot® personnel only. We strictly enforce our privacy policies with our employees and any breach of this policy will result in termination and the pressing of criminal charges where there are grounds.

### How we use your Personal Information

Your personal information will be used in order to provide you with the requested products and services. This includes the use of information for completing transactions or communicating back to you. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not used for any other purpose.

We may also use personal information in a manner that does not identify you specifically nor allow you to be contacted but does identify certain criteria about our Site's users in general (such as we may inform third parties about the number of registered users, number of unique visitors, and the pages most frequently browsed).

### Who we share your Personal Information with

We will NOT sell, trade or rent your name or personal information to anyone else. We DO NOT sell, trade, rent or provide outside access to our mailing list at all.

LawDepot® will not release your personal information to authorities unless required by law, search warrant, court order, subpoena, or fraud investigation.

Except as otherwise stated in this policy, LawDepot® will share your information with third parties only to the extent necessary to provide the services and products requested by you. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

### Collection of your Personal Information

LawDepot® only saves such personal information that is necessary for you to access and use our services. This personal information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, email address, phone number, other payment processing information and document creation data. LawDepot® will store such personal information until you delete that personal information through your “My Documents” or “My Account” pages on our site, you formally request its deletion or revoke your consent to its storage, or LawDepot® otherwise deletes that personal information in accordance with its decisions or internal policies.

### Document Preparation and Privacy of Information

The information you provide when you prepare a document on our website is held strictly confidential. For your protection provide a valid email address that will not block email from LawDepot®. To change your password, you must use the email address associated with your account. We do not give out passwords over the phone.

### Advertising

We partner with third party ad networks, such as Google Adwords, Bing Ads and Yahoo Gemini, to manage our advertising on other sites. Our Ad network partners use cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by using the following links: [Google's Opt-out](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/), [Bing's Opt-out](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/opt-out-of-the-bing-ads-optimization-program), [Yahoo's Opt-out](https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/us/en/optout/index.htm), or the [Network Advertising Initiative Opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

Please note that any opting-out will not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Third Party Services

This site uses the Google Maps API and the terms of [Google's Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy) are incorporated by reference into our Privacy Policy.
